ironfx.com 2015-03-18

# 

PRIVACY POLICY
Version: 25 October 2013
Copyright © 2013 IronFX. All Rights Reserved
                                             PRIVACY
                                              POLICY

                                                                              Privacy Policy
                                         PRIVACY POLICY
1.    Introduction
This Privacy Policy applies to all organizations within the IronFX Global group of companies
including IronFX Global Limited (“Company”). This Policy outlines how the Company
collects, maintains, uses and discloses personal information about you.
This Policy applies to existing and potential clients as well as to any visitors of the Company
website.
The Company is committed to protecting the privacy of all personal data which it obtains
from you, including information obtained during your visits to this website.
2.    Collection of Personal Data
The Company will only use your personal data in accordance with worldwide data protection
practices. The Company is registered as a Data Controller with the Office of the
Commissioner for Personal Data Protection under the Processing of Personal Data
(Protection of Individuals) Law 138(I)/2001 (the “Law”) and will process personal data only
in accordance with Cyprus data protection legislation, this Privacy Policy and the Trading
Terms and Conditions of the Company.
The Company will collect and hold personal data about you when you complete an online
application for a live or demo account or other type of form or when participating in any
other offer the Company promotes through this website.
The Company collects certain personal data in order that it may meet the needs of its
customers through the efficient provision of services. By collecting certain personal data, the
Company is able to monitor and improve the services which it offers to its existing and
potential customers.
Personal data collected includes but is not limited to:
       Personal details such as name, address, telephone number and/or e-mail address;
       Financial details such as estimated annual income and net worth, trading experience
        and investment knowledge;
       Identity Verification Documents such as passport and ID, utility bills, and/or bank
        statements or your company incorporation certificates/details.
The Company may derive information from your use of this website and may store this
information with your personal profile. This information may include site areas visited, pages
viewed, frequency and duration of visits, types of transactions conducted, documents
downloaded and other websites which may have referred you or to which you link.
3.    Use of Personal Data
The Company may use your information for any one or more of the following purposes:
Authorised and regulated by FCA • ASIC • DFSA • FSB • FSP • CRFIN • CySEC                       2

                                                                              Privacy Policy
        To confirm your identity;
        To maintain your personal profile;
        To assess your suitability to the products and services we provide;
        To provide the services to you that you have requested including processing
         transactions;
        To provide you with transaction and post transaction related services;
        To inform you of products and/or services that may be of interest to you;
        To keep you updated on the issues that are relevant to your business relationship with
         us;
        To tailor the website to your needs and interests;
        To analyze impersonalized statistical data to enable us to provide you with better
         products and/or services.
        To administer your account and monitor its conduct and assess and analyse any
         credit limit, including, the interest rate, fees and other charges to be applied to the
         Client’s Account;
        To pass your personal data to third parties for marketing purposes without prior
         written consent;
3.1 Retention of Personal Data
The Company will, as required by Law, retain your Personal Data on record for a period of at
least five (5) years, which is calculated after the execution of the transactions or the
termination of the business relationship or in case of termination of our business relationship.
3.2 Monitoring and Recording
The Company will, as required by Law, monitor and record any communication you have
with us whether in writing, by phone or by electronic mail.
3.3 Consent
You consent to the Company using your personal data for the above-stated purposes.
4.     Disclosure of Personal Data
The Company may be required to provide your personal data to the Cyprus Securities and
Exchange Commission and other regulatory and government bodies in Cyprus and other
countries as may be required by law from time to time.
The Company will disclose your Personal Data, without notice when required to do so by law
or in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) protect our rights and/or comply with any
court order or judicial proceedings; (b) avoid any potential fraud; (c) conform to the edicts of
the law or comply with a legal process served on the Company or on the Company’s website;
(d) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company (and Group Companies’)
websites, and, (e) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the
Company, its websites, or the public
Authorised and regulated by FCA • ASIC • DFSA • FSB • FSP • CRFIN • CySEC                        3

                                                                               Privacy Policy
4.1 The Company may also disclose your personal data to:
        The Company’s Introducing Brokers or any other Group Companies (“Processors”),
         who process data on behalf of the Company and who may only use it for the same
         purposes as the Company, subject to Clauses 4.2 and 4.3 below.
        Companies it hires to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging,
         mailing and delivering purchases, postal mail, etc. The Company will ensure that
         none of your Personal Data will be disseminated to those companies; the companies
         will only be subject to the information they need to deliver the service, and they are
         prohibited from using the information for any other purpose.
        financial institutions and other similar organizations that it deals with in the course of
         its corporate activities, or those that are nominated by you;
        external service providers and professional advisers (which may be located overseas)
         that provide services to the Company;
        any organisation at your request or any persons acting on your behalf, including your
         financial adviser, broker, solicitor or accountant;
        any third parties where this is necessary to process a transaction or provide services
         which you have requested; or
        any authority to whom the Company is required to disclose such information by law.
4.2 Warranties
The Processors shall ensure that:
    a. the Processor’s employees are informed of the confidential nature of the Personal
         Data; and
    b. it will process the Personal Data in compliance with all applicable laws, enactments,
         regulations, orders, standards and other similar instruments.
4.3 Indemnity
The Processors agree to indemnify and keep indemnified at its own expense the Company
against all costs, claims, damages or expenses incurred by the Company or for which the
Company may become liable due to any failure by the Processor or its Employees to comply
with any of its obligations under this Privacy Policy.
4.4 Statistical data
The Company may combine your personally identifiable data with information from other
users of this website to create impersonalized statistical data. The Company may provide this
statistical data to its business partners or third parties. In no circumstances will you be able to
be identified from this statistical data; you will remain anonymous.
5.     Your Rights
You are not obligated to provide any of the personal data requested by the Company. In the
absence of this information, however, the Company may not be able to open an account for
Authorised and regulated by FCA • ASIC • DFSA • FSB • FSP • CRFIN • CySEC                           4

                                                                            Privacy Policy
you where the information is requested in on an application form, or to provide you with any
other services, information or assistance you have sought.
Under the Cyprus data protection legislation, you have (subject to certain exceptions) the
right to request any personal data the Company holds about you and to inform the Company
of any perceived inaccuracy. We may charge a fee to cover the associated administrative
costs.
You may inform the Company at any time that your personal details have changed or that you
wish the Company to delete personal data we hold about you by emailing us
at compliance@IronFX.com. The Company will change or delete your personal data in
accordance with your instructions, except to the extent that we are required to hold your
personal data for regulatory or legal purposes, to provide you with the services you have
requested or to maintain adequate business records.
If you have any questions, complaints or requests, please write to the Company, verifying
your identity and setting out in full what information you require. If a complaint is not
resolved by the Company to your satisfaction, you may complain to the Information
Commissioner.
6.     Consent
By accessing this website, you consent to the Company collecting, maintaining, using and
disclosing personal data about you and provided by you or by another person as in
accordance with this Privacy Policy.
7.     Links
When you use this website, you may be able to link to other websites. This Privacy Policy
does not apply to those other sites. The Company encourages you to read and understand the
privacy policies on these other sites.
8.     Cookies
The Company uses cookies to gather information about your access to our website and other
services we provide to you. Please note that this description is not comprehensive and the
Company’s Cookie Policy contains additional information.
Cookies are small pieces of information which use a unique identification tag and are stored
on your device as a result of you using this website or other services we provide to you.
Most internet browsers are set up to accept cookies. If you do not wish to receive cookies,
you may be able to change the settings of your browser to refuse all cookies or to have your
computer notify you each time a cookie is sent to it, and thereby give yourself the choice
whether to accept it or not. However, it is strongly recommended that you allow cookies on
our website to ensure you have the best possible experience. Turning off cookies may result
in reduced performance of our website and trading platform and may also impair the quality
of the services that we provide to you in relation to your account.
Authorised and regulated by FCA • ASIC • DFSA • FSB • FSP • CRFIN • CySEC                    5

                                                                                    Privacy Policy
9.     Security
The Company adopts strong measures to protect the security of your Personal Data and to
ensure it is not accessed by unauthorised persons. Access to Personal Data is restricted to
employees and authorized service providers who need it to perform their work. You must not
share or disclose your log in details with any third party.
The Company takes strong precautions to protect your personal data from loss, theft, copying,
misuse, unauthorised access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Measures include
encryption during data transmission, strong authentication mechanisms and separation of
machines and data to provide secure areas.
10.    Amendments to policy
The Company reserves the right to make changes this Privacy Policy from time to time for
any reason and will notify you of such changes by posting an updated version of this Privacy
Policy on this website. You are responsible for regularly reviewing this Privacy Policy and if
you use this website after any such changes are published, such use shall constitute your
agreement to such changes.
All queries should be emailed to us at compliance@IronFX.com.
Version: 20 January 2015
Copyright © 2015 IronFX. All Rights Reserved
                                            IronFX Global Limited,
                         2, Iapetou Street, Agios Athanasios, 4101 Limassol, Cyprus
                                  Tel: +357 25027000 | Fax: +357 25027001
                              Email: info@ironfx.com | Web: www.IronFX.com
Authorised and regulated by FCA • ASIC • DFSA • FSB • FSP • CRFIN • CySEC                          6
